

# SOMYA RANJAN NAYAK

# About Me

I am a dynamic graduate with 1.5 years of experience in marketing and 6 months in finance sector. I am a digital marketing specialist With a solid background in technology and a passion for continuous learning.



(+91) 9337319960



somyanayak281@gmail.com



Bhubaneswar, Odisha

**SKILLS** 

- Digital Marketing
- Google Adwords/ Ads
- Data Analytics
- SEO
- Email Marketing
- Wordpress
- Web development
- Java
- Python
- Financial Modeling
- Financial Management
- Company valuation
- Account based Marketing
- Social Media

Management

## **EXPERIENCE**

Fidelity International (2021) - Investment manager Intern

JP Morgan (2021 - 2022) - Market virtual experience Intern

Highradius (2022- 2023) - Marketing and treasury - Mid-market ABM Intern

### **EDUCATION**

10th - Dav public school, Paradeep (2017) CGPA - 10

12th - Mothers public school, Bhubaneswar (2019)

CGPA - 7.5

BTech (CSIT) - Institute of Technical Education and Research, Bhubaneswar (2019 - 2023)

CGPA - 7.8

#### **PROJECTS**

Financial Models of Dabur and Walmart

Python projects

Web development projects

**CFA Investment foundation Program**